Music by Ryan . . .
.
BIRDS CHIRP
Oh, my God.
Ah!
Hell Fist!
Junction! Hell Fist! Hell Fist!
I'll be back with you.
All of us, we're going
to be back with you.
I won't be able to fight you.
There's no way we can fight you.
I'll be back with you.
You'll be back with us.
How is that possible?
They left Garp on Pirate Island?
What happened to him?
The article says he went there
to rescue some guy named Kobe.
I guess he succeeded.
Too bad it cost him his life.
Where does it say he's dead?
The man's a living legend.
This isn't how he's gonna go.
I push looks off your faces. You're right.
I'm sure he's fine.
Damn right he is.
Who's laughing?
You think this is funny?
Oh, sweetheart.
Don't worry.
He didn't mean it.
There, there.
Oh, it was just the baby.
I'm sorry, Machado.
You're worried about Garp too, aren't you?
Was that what you were laughing at?
You know Luffy's face now, don't you?
We love Luffy. Yes, we do.
What the hell are those idiots thinking?
Oh, we've got a big one!
It's an earthquake!
It's a tsunami!
It's a heartbreak!
Follow me!
The earthquake on that day was
unlike any other in recorded history.
It caused devastating
damage all around the world.
We're too late!
The situation was highly unusual.
The earthquake's epicenter
could not be detected.
The truth was hidden from the public.
But it was no coincidence that the
tragedy occurred six days after
the kingdom of Lucia was wiped off
the map by the world government.
I'm at the remains of Lucia!
There is no trace of the land anymore!
Just a giant hole swallowing up the sea!
No further approach is possible!
The hole isn't milling!
Across the entire world,
sea levels rose by approximately one meter
following the havoc of the earthquake.
The beach has never flooded like this!
At this rate, there won't be
any beach left here at all!
Why isn't the tide pulling back?
This is too cruel!
Running on the beach is
our favorite pastime!
Give it back!
This isn't glamorous at all!
A number of beaches have disappeared from
the world, along with several islands.
There's nothing left for us here.
We have to go!
My shark swim right into my house!
It's not supposed to be high tide yet.
Might make for a big catch, though.
You really want to go
sailing in this mess?
Sir, an update on the flooding situation.
Sea levels are rising around the world.
Yes, sir, but the cause is unclear.
Meanwhile, Egghead was surrounded by a
fleet of 100 Navy vessels of various sizes,
including 20 massive battleships.
This was a force that
could level a nation,
with power far exceeding
even that of a Buster Call.
The total number of Marines was 30,000.
And the leaders of this
unprecedented operation...
...were nine Navy HQ vice-amirals.
and Admiral Chizuru.
We're under attack!
Hey, I told you not to
attack the sea-beast weapons!
I heard you, but I'm
afraid to detect us first.
Your milk, he's over, sir.
Oh, my favorite.
There you go.
Eat it while it's hot.
Mmm.
Huh?
I gotta say, you're really putting
me on the spot here, you said tomato.
Why don't you just surrender and
have a nice bowl of ramen with me?
Get serious.
Attack again and we'll open fire.
Ooh, now you're scaring me.
You know what you're up against here.
Punk developed the pacifista's
lasers by studying your power.
Wow, so cool!
Now you're here to murder him.
Never thought things
would turn out this way.
He studied the void century, Sentomaru.
Old friend or not, I can't
defend a crime like that.
In the end, I'm just the Navy's puppet.
That said we don't want to have
this battle any more than you do.
The more we destroy the more we lose.
I was really hoping Luchi would clean this
up quickly without trashing the place.
You can thank the Straw Hats for that one.
Don't let anyone else know I'm here.
Yes sir.
The Straw Hats took Vagabond hostage.
and barricaded themselves inside.
I like this article.
It's Morgan's work.
And what is the truth?
Sir, we haven't received word that
CP0 has completed their mission.
Sentumatu is prepared to
defend the island outside,
so we can guess who's in the labophase.
First, we have Dr.
Vegapunk, along with his six satellites.
They should have the Four
Seraphim protecting them.
Then there's Straw Hat Luffy and his crew,
who seem to have allied with the Doctor.
Also,
there's CP-0's Wabluci, along with the
others in his leading unit, Kaku and Stussy.
As for the other Cypherpole agents,
they appear to have been
captured by Sentomaru
and his pacifistas in the Fabrio phase.
One added note.
The Frontier Dome's barrier
status is currently at 100%,
meaning that no one can enter
or leave the Lobby phase.
It's been like that for an entire day.
We still don't know
what's going on inside.
What happened to all
the research staff and
technicians who were employed on Egghead?
They're not present.
They evacuated the island yesterday.
We've already located their ships.
And what if they know too much?
Sink them at once.
Yes, sir.
Just one more thing first.
We spotted Jewelry Bonnie.
She may be there with the Straw Hats.
Kuma's daughter, you say?
We have no more use for her.
Forget about her.
She's just a girl.
Yes, sir.
Admiral, sir!
What?
I'm trying to enjoy a meal here.
We're picking up a signal
coming from Egghead.
A signal.
They seem to be making a call somewhere.
We'll find out who they're calling then.
It's Marie Joie!
Who is this?
Admiral, you should have a black
transponder snail on your wrist.
Oh.
You can tap the call.
Whoa.
Yeah, hello, it's me! York!
You're still alive.
That's all you have to say?
Are you Pangaea kidding me?
What the hell are you
trying to kill me, too?
I'm the one who told you what Stella did.
Remember that, Pops?
Be that as it may, you're still
a Vegapunk, just like the others.
I don't give a shit
about the Void Century.
And even if I did, you think I
would have tipped you off about it?
You debate!
Fair enough.
But how did you survive?
Did CP0 fail at their mission?
And what is the status of the Straw Hats?
Well, I'm still here.
That alone should tell
you how the others are.
I'm no one calling the shots now.
An egghead is mine.
All mine.
You know what that means?
If your skin bags try to
backstab me again, I call...
The Big Guns!
Oh, for Seraphim.
Now...
About your little fleet
surrounding the island.
You trying to start a
war with me or something?
We could be convinced to
alter our plans, York.
But let me confirm one thing first.
Can you create the Mother Flame yourself?
Oh, now they want to negotiate.
I'm glad I sent you that sample.
I knew you'd get hooked
once you had a piece.
It is of the highest priority.
Whose priority, I wonder?
Too bad this island's the only
power plant that makes it.
Here's the sitch.
Promise that me and the lab will
make it out of this thing unscathed.
Agreed.
And make me a celestial
dragon while you're at it.
It shall be done.
Then we've got ourselves a deal.
One more thing.
I need you to come and save me!
Straw Luffy is here!
And he's gonna kill me!
What? What's this?
What's going on in there?
Hey, Luffy.
What should we do with this one?
No more use for her now, right? No!
Spass them all dead! No!
No! Do it now! Please!
What a disaster this has been.
I've caused you all such trouble. Sorry.
Eh, we forgive you.
But she is a different story.
So, Luffy, what's the plan for her?
They wanna keep her alive, right?
Let's use her as a
shield when we run away.
So, it's like a hostage situation, huh?
Talk to me, Doc.
She gonna be okay?
It'll take time for her wounds to heal,
but with plenty of rest, she'll be fine.
Hello!
Huh?
My name is Monkey D.
Luffy, and I'm gonna
be king of the pirates!
That's what you choose to open with?
What is wrong with you?
We have Dr.
Vegapunk, all the Vegapunks even!
If you want to save York's life, clear
your ships from the shore, every last one.
You don't understand.
What is he doing?
No, Luffy? Why?
That story was fake.
So you're Straw Hat Luffy? Are you?
Have you suffered any
casualties in the lab?
Who is still there with you?
Well, uh, let me see.
A couple of people are hurt.
Kali.
A woman's voice.
Must be Nico Robin.
Why'd you make me hang up?
Intel is a weapon.
You must never give it to your enemies.
Oh, right. Sorry.
But hey, the ships will be gone now.
What the hell they will?
You think the Navy's that dumb?
What's our next move?
There are three things we must protect.
York's safety, the data
stored inside punk records,
and the power plant that
creates the Mother Flame.
Everything else is expendable.
But sir, Rob Lucci and the other Cypherpole
agents are still trapped inside there.
We might face a worst-case scenario.
We must prioritize accordingly.
regard humans as you
regard insects even if
you exterminate some
they'll multiply again!
Yes sir you listen to
me you tiny terrorists
I need a pact with the five elders you get
it hurt me and you die
what they do to this
island will make Uhura
look like fireworks!
That hurt!
You're gonna pay!
I'll sic the elders on you first!
Yeah?
Go right ahead!
You're lucky that's all you got!
How dare you say that in front of Robin!
Keep your filthy mouth shut!
She can't hurt us.
Just ignore her.
Robin are you feeling okay? Of course.
Have you met my doctor?
He's brilliant
Pretty pathetic display though to be fair.
I was fighting to Sarah him at once
You need to rest
Oh, my God!
Could you quiet down for a sec?
What?
I'm trying to get in contact
with the basement right now.
Hey, can you guys hear me?
Everyone's still alive?
Thank you, Straw Hats!
We can finally eat again!
You saved us!
We were losing hope!
So good!
I'm alive!
Man, do I love the Straw Hat crew!
That's so loud, buddy.
We're still enemies.
Now, is there any chance you
could let us out of this room?
I'm glad everyone's okay, but we
really can't do that right now, sorry.
Fair enough, but could you relocate us?
It's kind of nerve-wracking in here
with them around. What's wrong?
Are you guys afraid of the Seraphim?
They're supposed to be on the same
side as you guys, aren't they?
And now, what if they go berserk?
Hey, there's nothing to
worry about, is there?
No, they're safe.
Those bubble balls are
made of the same material
as the Pacifista Mark
III's bubble shields.
They're resilient enough
to deflect cannon blasts.
They're also created with sea energy,
making them the perfect prison to
contain those with Devil Fruit powers.
Oh, I thought they were
just regular bubbles.
How dare you trap me in this damn thing?
It is foolish to be afraid of us!
We do our job and none of the
Seraphim were ordered to kill you.
You're of no interest to us
Then
Now I just feel silly?
Don't buy the suits, Snake.
They're just chomping.
You're super cool in our book
after what you did before
Thanks for turning us back
from stone little sister.
She really did that?
How peculiar.
Unless I made an error, that behavior
should not be in the programming.
Come on! Please, Hancock!
They're my friends!
You've got to undo this stone thing now!
You're the only person who
can save them, so please!
Alright, fine!
I'll undo it!
Just please stop staring at me like that!
Oh, I see how it is.
She's just as unmanageable
as the original Hancock,
with the same soft spot for Luffy.
This is too funny.
Ooh.
I didn't know Seraphim worked that way.
Oh, hi, Hancock.
How's it going?
It seems the information
transmitted through
bloodline elements is
broader than I thought.
Fascinating.
You were super awesome back there.
I owe you.
I owe you. What? What?
Did you just say I love you?
Hey, Stella, we've got trouble.
The communication system's
been fully restored,
but the Frontier Dome still
won't open for some reason.
Don't even bother.
I protected the dome with a passcode,
but my brain's not synced
with all of you anymore.
And I'm not telling!
Oh, yeah!
And I beat it out of your bed!
Lilith, no!
While all of you lose your
minds, I'm gonna rest easy.
Now, go fetch me a snack.
Snap on my fists, you big fists!
If we can't deactivate the
bed, then we hopped escape.
After all my smooth tucking,
I thought we were free.
Yeah, you're a real diplomat.
or seriously injured two of
agapunk satellites dead as for the
Straw Hats you're mumbling what's
wrong just talking to myself
i checked outside and were completely
surrounded in all directions
hello Stussy it looks like 100 ships i'd
assume there are around 30 000 marines
My, this is quite the event.
Welcome back, my darling.
Care for a cup of coffee?
Why, thank you.
Stop glaring at me.
You're Nami, correct?
The cruise navigator?
Uh-huh, that's me.
How does a route look? Uh,
the log post hasn't recorded a signal, but
we still have one steady needle from 1L.
Seems we'll be going northeast.
Ah, that would be Elbaf.
Elbaf, really?
We're going! Finally!
Guess so, yeah.
And what's there?
The Giants!
Why are they so excited about this?
We do have one advantage.
Your ship is up here in the
Lobby phase within our grasp.
The Navy ships are
offshore in all directions.
It would be impossible
to sail out to the port.
You said that we'll be
heading to the northeast.
That's the back side of the island.
Luckily, your ship is waiting
right next to the Vega Force One.
With a little rocket propulsion,
it should be able to carry us
clean over the Navy blockade.
On the downside, Vega Force One can only
fly within the airspace over Egghead.
So let's hope we get enough distance
before we take a north dive.
There's no way that'll be far enough.
I gotcha, Zack.
Doc,
you just do the best you can,
then the Sunnies coup de burst
will carry us the rest of the way.
We'll fly a whole kilometer.
No way they'll catch us after that.
My goodness.
How in the world can your ship fly so far?
Cool-a-power, Vegapro.
Cool-a-power?
I love it.
That sounds like a plan.
Ah, yeah.
Can you head to Vega Force One now?
I know what you're thinking.
You want me to move the Straw Hat's ship
to the backside of the island, right?
I'll help, too.
But we still can't go anywhere till
we deactivate the darn Frontier Dome.
And I'm never gonna hand over the code.
We'll crack it!
We'll crack the pumpkin!
Seems like our plan is
coming together nicely.
I bet there's absolutely zero chance
we pull this off without a hitch.
That's all we got.
We don't know till we try.
Yeah, that's true enough.
If you're going to the city, take me with.
That is my baby after all. Take me too!
I can't wait to see Elbow!
Hey, let me help out!
Oh, so cute.
Ready?
Full speed ahead!
It's time to go!
Let's get your ship to
the backside, quick.
Knowing them, they'll have
that frontier dome down soon.
That might be good, or it might
just cause even more problems.
I don't get it.
Why wouldn't you want it down?
Because there's a catch.
If we can get out, the feds can get in.
If we're not ready to rock when
it opens, we're in trouble.
Oh, I see now.
This is so much fun.
I've never left Egghead.
World, here I come.
Come on, Doc, this ain't a road trip.
I just thought of something.
We're gonna need so much more food.
Oh, yeah, you're right.
We'll eat all of this in one day.
Do we even have pizzas?
Crap, that's super important.
We have to get a ton of cheese.
I think we have everything else
Sanji needs to make them for us.
Really?
That guy's pretty cool, huh?
He's a good cook and a good fighter.
Huh, this is weird.
What's got you in such a
happy mood all of a sudden?
Earlier you wanted to kill old man Apple.
You're right, I did.
But I'm over that now.
That's good.
So why were you crying all night?
We've received a transmission from Lucci.
We know the situation inside the dome.
Now share it with the other ships.
Yes sir.
Did you hear that, Borsalino?
Uh-huh.
He talked a big game,
but it seems he doesn't have quite
as much leverage as he implied.
In fact, all of them are
trapped in that dome like rats.
If it uses a laser defense system,
can't you simply pass through it?
You are like itself, are you not?
Well, the barrier isn't
what's stopping me.
There's a friend of mine waiting on the
shore and he's determined
to protect Vegapunk.
Why not fly over him?
I can't disrespect a man who's
putting everything on the line.
I like to think I'm cooler than that.
At the very least, let me
stick to my principles.
And remember,
since Amaru is poised to attack,
the second we make a move he'll order
every resource at his command into action.
That means a swarm of sea beast
weapons and 50 Pacifistas.
Bad news for all the ships we brought.
We'll be committing to
a massive bloodbath.
We better settle this quickly.
Do we know where the power plant is?
Our friend Lucci hasn't
been sleeping on the job.
We have all the information we need, and
he delivered it straight to our door.
Six Power Masters, proceed to
land as soon as the battle begins!
Our mission is to free the
captured cyberbull agents!
Artillery fire won't
work on the pacifesians!
AIM ALL CANDONS AT THE
SEAT-RAISED WEAPONS!
It sure is fine!
Just like on Sky Island!
I love this place too,
but we gotta lock it!
Made it! Where's the Sunny?
No turning back.
Secret Yata Mirror.
What the? He's here. Let's go!
Pacifistas!
I won't go easy on you!
Simplomaru!
Bring it on, uncle!
You're facing the strongest
defense in the whole world!
What?
What's going on?
Where is this light coming from?
Someone's here!
Someone's strong!
Thank you.